{
    "quizes": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "name": "quiz1",
        "description": "This is the quiz #1",
        "questions": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "type": "single",
              "question": "ერთპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4"
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "type": "multiple",
              "question": "მრავალპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2"
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "type": "boolean",
              "question": "დისკრეტული კითხვა"
            }
          ],
          "answers": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "answer": 3
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "answer": [
                2,
                4
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "answer": true
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "name": "quiz2",
        "description": "this is quiz #2",
        "questions": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "type": "single",
              "question": "ერთპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4"
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "type": "multiple",
              "question": "მრავალპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2"
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "type": "boolean",
              "question": "დისკრეტული კითხვა"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "type": "single",
                "question": "ერთპასუხიანი კითხვა",
                "options": [
                  "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1^",
                  "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2^",
                  "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3^",
                  "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4^"
                ]
              }
          ],
          "answers": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "answer": 3
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "answer": [
                2,
                4
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "answer": true
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "answer": 2
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "name": "quiz3",
        "description": "This is the quiz #3",
        "questions": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "type": "single",
              "question": "ერთპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4"
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "type": "multiple",
              "question": "მრავალპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2"
              ]
            }
          ],
          "answers": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "answer": 3
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "answer": [
                2,
                4
              ]
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "name": "quiz4",
        "description": "this is quiz #4",
        "questions": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "type": "single",
              "question": "ერთპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4"
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "type": "multiple",
              "question": "მრავალპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 4",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2"
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "type": "boolean",
              "question": "დისკრეტული კითხვა"
            },
            {
              "id": 4,
              "type": "boolean",
              "question": "დისკრეტული კითხვა"
            },
            {
              "id": 5,
              "type": "multiple",
              "question": "მრავალპასუხიანი კითხვა",
              "options": [
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი ^3",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 1",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი ^4",
                "სავარაუდო პასუხი 2"
              ]
            }
          ],
          "answers": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "answer": 3
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "answer": [
                2,
                4
              ]
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "answer": true
            },
            {
              "id": 4,
              "answer": false
            },
            {
              "id": 5,
              "answer": [
                1,
                3
              ]
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "name": "quiz5",
        "description": "this is quiz #5",
        "questions": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "type": "boolean",
              "question": "დისკრეტული კითხვა"
            }
          ],
          "answers": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "answer": true
            }
          ]
    }
    ]
}